{
  "status": true,
  "data": [{
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Social Engineering",
    "details": [{
      "question": "What is the Goal of social Engineering",
      "options": [
        "Sabotage a person’s social media",
        "To gain vital personal information",
        "To catfish someone",
        "To build trust"
      ],
      "answer": "To gain vital personal information"
    },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following are examples of social engineering scams executed via phishing?",
        "options": [
          "Banking Link Scams",
          "Facebook Message Link Scams",
          "Fax Notice Scams",
          "All the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Reconnaissance?",
        "options": [
          "gaining and discovering information about a system",
          "malicious software that is being developed by cybercriminals",
          "program installed on your computer without your knowledge",
          "computer is being compromised by malware"
        ],
        "answer": "gaining and discovering information about a system"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the objective of a network reconnaissance attack?",
        "options": [
          "Unauthorized manipulation of data",
          "Disabling network system or services",
          "Discovery and mapping of systems",
          "Denying access to resources by legitimate users"
        ],
        "answer": "Discovery and mapping of systems"
      }
    ]
  },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "title": "Malware",
      "details": [{
        "question": "What is malware?",
        "options": [
          "a program",
          "an antivirus",
          "an operating system",
          "software intended to damage or disable computers or computer systems"
        ],
        "answer": "software intended to damage or disable computers or computer systems"
      },
        {
          "question": "How does a computer virus infect a pc?",
          "options": [
            "Suspicious web links",
            "Email attachments",
            "Attached to files on memory sticks",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
          "question": "What does a Trojan Horse do?",
          "options": [
            "deletes everything on a user’s computer",
            "stores information",
            "transfers data and information",
            "gives malicious users remote control over a user’s compute"
          ],
          "answer": "gives malicious users remote control over a user’s compute"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is an example of adware?",
          "options": [
            "Google",
            "Twitter",
            "DeskAd",
            "Snapchat"
          ],
          "answer": "DeskAd"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "title": "Cyber Attacks",
      "details": [{
        "question": "What are the measures to manage cyber-attacks?",
        "options": [
          "update Software",
          "System Backup",
          "maintain Privilege and Accounts",
          "All the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All the above"
      },
        {
          "question": "Staff should only be educated about Social engineering?",
          "options": [
            "Yes",
            "No",
            "",
            ""
          ],
          "answer": "No"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}